trafficncash.com 2016-04-05

# TrafficNcash-Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or  
subscribe to our newsletter. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate,  
you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, or mailing address.

**What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To process transactions your information, whether public or private, will not be sold,  
exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without  
your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or  
service requested.

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature To send periodic emails.

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information  
and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news,  
updates, related product or service information, etc.

**How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information  
when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally  
identifiable information. We may release your information when we believe release  
is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours  
or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor  
information maybe provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Do we use cookies?**  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers  
hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers  
systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and Affiliates. If you have any additional  
questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact us via our Support page.

**Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services  
on our website. Members and advertisers also display third party content and links as  
included with purchased services on our website.

These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore  
have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked  
sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any  
feedback about these sites.
